HAZEL TIFFANY C. TAYLO

Malagasang 1G, Imus, Cavite, 4103 | 09776958441 | hazeltiffany.taylo@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A self-motivated BS in Computer Engineering specialized in Software Engineering graduate proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Microsoft SQL Server, and mySQL. I am equipped with an eagerness to learn to improve in the field of web development. Able to effectively work alone in projects as well as collaborative setup.

EDUCATION

De La Salle University- Dasmariñas

August 2018 – September 2023

BS in Computer Engineering specialized in Software Engineering

GPA: 3.22

KodeGoFull-stack Web Development Bootcamp

January 2023- July 2023

KEY SKILLS

Programming

HTML and CSS, JavaScript, SQL, PHP, Python, and C++

Languages:

Tools:

Teams, Google Workspace, Zoom, Github, Microsoft Office, Figma, Canva, Trello,

VS Code

WORK EXPERIENCE

Concentrix CVG Philippines Inc.

October 2019 - August 2022

Customer Service Representative, Advisor I

- Responded to customer queries effectively while maintaining my metrics above the goal.
- Executed friendliness, professionalism, and enthusiasm in assisting customers and for the company's mission.

RELEVANT INTERNSHIPS

FEdCenter (Finance Education Center)

March 2023 – June 2023

Project IT, Back-end Web Developer

- Tools Used: HTML and CSS, JavaScript, Microsoft SQL Server and PHP
- Created the login, and time-in and time-out system of the company.
- Led the team in the organization of files.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Dream Maker

February 2023 - March 2023

- Tools Used: HTML and CSS, Bootstrap, and GitHub
- Provided Front-end codes during web development from scratch.

KodeGo - Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Burgers Galore April 2023 – June 2023

• Tools Used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery, API, and GitHub

- Provided Front-end and Back-end codes during web development.
- Led the team, building Front-end and Back-end from scratch.

De La Salle University- Dasmariñas - Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering ThesisVermiWeb January 2023 - June 2023

- Tools Used: HTML, CSS, PHP, MSSQL, and mySQL
- Provided Front-end and Back-end codes during web development.
- Led the team, building Front-end and Back-end from scratch.

CERTIFICATIONS

TOEIC Certificate: with score of 895 **KodeGo Bootcamp Certificate**

February 2023 January 2023 - July 2023

RELEVANT LINKS

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hazeltiffanytaylo/

Jobs180: https://hazeltiffanytaylo.jobs180.com/

Portfolio: https://tayloportfoliowebsites.github.io/HTTIFFYPortfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/imhazeltaylo/